{
["data"{"Question" : "Which year did Carnival begin cruising?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1.1970",
  "2": "2. 1972",
  "3": "3.1969",
  "Answer" : "3"
]
  ["data"{"Question" : "In Camp Ocean, the 6-8 year old group is known as which animal?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. Penguins",
  "2":  "2. Stingrays",
  "3": "3. Dolphins",
  "Answer" : "2"
  ]
  ["data"{"Question" : "How many ships are in Carnival's Fantasy class?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. 4",
  "2":  "2. 8",
  "3": "3.9",
  "Answer" : "2"
  ]
  ["data"{"Question" : "Which of the following ships are NOT a part of Carnival's Dream class?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. Carnival Vista, Valor, and Imagination",
  "2":  "2. Carnival Vista, Breeze, and Valor",
  "3":  "3. Carnival Imagination, Breeze, and Magic ",
  "Answer" : "1"
  ]
  ["data"{"Question" : "Which Carnival Ship has fake eagles behind glass cases?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. Carnival Vista",
  "2":  "2. Carnival Valor",
  "3": "3. Carnival Magic",
  "Answer" : "2"
  ]
  ["data"{"Question" : "What is the deck for Lido Deck?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. 8",
  "2":  "2. 9",
  "3": "3. 10",
  "Answer" : "3"
          ]

  ]  ["data"{"Question" : "Which of the following Carnival ships will begin sailing from Tampa, Florida, in 2018??",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. Carnival Legend",
  "2":  "2. Carnival Miracle",
  "3":  "3. Carnival Paradise",
  "Answer" : "2"
          ]
  ]  ["data"{"Question" : "The name of Carnival's 2018 newbuild is the _______________________?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. Carnival Horizon",
  "2":  "2. Carnival Reflection",
  "3":  "3. Carnival Sunshine",
  "Answer" : "1










  ]  ["data"{"Question" : "Which Northern Ports of Call is named after a female name?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. Victoria",
  "2":  "2. Anastasia",
  "3": "3. Elizabeth",
  "Answer" : "1"
  }
          [
  ]  ["data"{"Question" : "Which Island is named after a celestial being?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. Half Moon Cay",
  "2":  "2. Puerto Rico",
  "3": "3. Hawaii",
  "Answer" : "1"
          ]

  ]  ["data"{"Question" : "Which Island was famous in the 1988 Olympics?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. Haiti",
  "2":  "2. Jamaica",
  "3":  "3. Trinidad ",
  "Answer" : "2"
  ]
  ["data"{"Question" : "True or False, are the island named after male names the British Virgin Islands?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. True",
  "2":  "2. False",
  "Answer" : "1"
  ]
  ["data"{"Question" :  "Which island has local ruins Cahal Pech, Altun Ha, or Xuananunich?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. Puerto Rico",
  "2":  "2. Belize",
  "3": "3. Costa Rica",
  "Answer" : "2"
  ]
  ["data"{"Question" : "Where is the tallest mountain in the Virgin Islands?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1. St Maarten",
  "2":  "2. Jamaica",
  "3":  "3. Tortola",
  "Answer" : "3"
  ]
  ["data"{"Question" : "Which South American city was founded by Rodrigo de Bastidas in 1525?",
  "Category": "Cruise",
  "1" : "1.Venezuela",
  "2": "2. Columbia",
  "3": "3. Panama",
  "Answer" : "2"
  ]




}
